# DAJANA MUHO

☑ dajana\_muho@yahoo.com

**(**779) 270-4311

• Harrison, NJ 07029

% <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>GitHub</u>

#### SKILLS

- Programming: Python, Node.js, React,
  JavaScript, Hadoop, Bootstrap, Microservices
- DBMS: Mongo dB, MySQL, Oracle, Redis
- Cloud Data Warehouse (Big Query)
- Data Analysis and Visualization (Tableau, Google Data Studio)
- Neuro-linguistic programming
- Neural Networks (TensorFlow)
- Algorithm Design
- Data Structures
- Data mining
- Unified Modelling Language
- Big Data Analytics Life Cycle

#### **EDUCATION**

Master of Science: Data Science Graduate Center, City University of New York May 2023

#### Projects:

- Q&A Chatbot- Building a machine learning chatbot using NLP to accurately predict the correct answers to questions.
- Data Visualization- Visualization of the US immigrants' trends by using Tableau and Python libraries.
- Sentiment Analysis- Build a machine learning model to predict the positivity and the negativity of the tweets
- Insurance Management System- MERN project supported by ML algorithms to predict customer behaviour and help insurance companies by analyzing and measuring risks.

**Bachelor of Science**: Computer Science University of Tirana Sep 2016 - Jul 2019 (GPA 3.86/4)

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Complex problem-solver with an analytical and driven mindset. Currently pursuing an MS in Data Science with a passion for building models that tackle complex challenges. Experienced full-stack developer in agile environments, who can work autonomously as well as in collaboration with different teams. Motivated to learn, grow, and excel.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

### AIRFIND – FULL-STACK DEVELOPER 08/2020 - Current

- Build, test, and deploy scalable, highly available, and modular software products using Node.js, Next.js, and React.
- Revise, modularize, and update old code bases to modern development standards, reducing operating costs and improving functionality.
- Set up and work on a microservice environment using Docker.
- Create Unit and Integration tests to ensure the quality of code.
- Create technical workflows and knowledge base for training purposes.
- Collaborated with infrastructure engineers and system administrators in designing big-data infrastructures using MongoDB and Big Query.

# UNIVERSITY OF TIRANA, SCIENTIFIC GROUP - MEMBER 11/2020 - 06/2021

- Designed and analyzed information from controller laboratory-based investigations, experiments using statistical techniques.
- Developed and implemented databases and data collection systems.

### KREATX – FULL-STACK DEVELOPER 09/2019 - 05/2021

- Built Low-Code platform using Node.js and Vanilla JS.
- Assisted throughout the development lifecycle from requirement gathering to production releases.
- Administered, supported, and monitored databases by proactively resolving database issues and maintaining servers.

## IMB – FULL-STACK DEVELOPER 02/2019 - 08/2019

 Built a MERN stack-based project and expanded into platforms and protocols such as REST and databases.